affiliatexfiles.com 2015-04-06

# Affiliatexfiles Privacy Policy – AffiliateXFiles

### Affiliate X Files Privacy Policy

Last Updated: Friday, November 28, 2011

Our Privacy Policy covers the security and usage of any and all personal or business information that is collected and stored when you submit a subscription request, or request information via email from Affiliatexfiles.com.

Other than the information requested in our online forms, no other personal information is collected from visitors to our web site.

Our privacy policy does not apply to the practices of other websites or companies advertised on our site, or otherwise listed, nor does it extend to people or entities that Affiliatexfiles.com does not employ or manage.

**Collection and Use of Information**

Affiliate X Files only collects minimal personal or business information when you subscribe or request additional Information from our site. The only information collected in these instances is your Name, and Email Address.

Unless it is a business proposal then maybe a contact phone number may be required or business address.

Affiliate X Files has to date not used any email address information for any other purpose, but reserves the right to deliver notices via the website or email messages to subscribers regarding modifications or updates to the Affiliatexfiles.com website or services.

**Sharing and Disclosure of Personal or Business Information**

[Affiliate X Files](http://www.affiliatexfiles.com/ "Affiliate X Files Home") secures your contact information such as your email address and other relevant information on our server. Your personal subscription information is never released to or sold to any vendor, partner or outside agency.

Any emails, marketing newsletters or website announcements that are sent from Affiliatexfiles.com will include detailed unsubscribe information at the bottom of such email, giving you the option to unsubscribe yourself from future mailings at any time.

**Email and Personal Security**

Your personal or business email address and contact information will be stored in a protected directory on our server. Access is restricted to the management only.

**Google’s Double Click DART Cookie:**

This website may contain Ads by Google. They have recently instituted the new “interest-based advertising”, which allows them to serve ads they think will be of interest to you personally. This is done by placing a cookie on your computer whenever you visit a website, such as this one, that serves Ads by Google.

This cookie can contain information ( NOT including your name, address, email address, or telephone number ) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice, or if you would like to opt out of Google’s use of the DART cookie, visit [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google Ad Content Network Privacy Policy").

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Affiliate X Files might change our privacy policy from time to time and without consultation. If major changes are made in a way that your personal information could be used, we will post a prominent announcement on our website Affiliatexfiles.com notifying you as a subscriber of the change.

Allowing you the option to unsubscribe from our mailing list and any further communications.

Thanking You For Your Time ,
